Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Kelly Miller Smith Papers
1985
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0400
66.78 linear_feet
Acknowledgments
Conversations that took place at Vanderbilt University among Peter Paris, Dorothy Parks, Alice Smith, Kelly Miller Smith, Jr., and Marice Wolfe during the Spring and Summer of 1985 culminated in the official transfer of the Kelly Miller Smith Papers to safekeeping at Vanderbilt on 11 December 1985.
Anticipating the development, the Heard Library Society provided funds for Divinity graduate student Marcia Riggs to arrange and begin description of the collection. Her knowledge and sympathetic understanding of the mission of Kelly Miller Smith made her a particularly fine cataloger of the papers. Archivist Sara Harwell of Special Collections directed the project, and designed and edited the Register.
In addition to the Papers deposited by the Smith family, there are nearly 100 plaques and certificates paying tribute to Smith, and a second series of archival records from Smith's Divinity School office. Some of the tributes are on exhibit at Kelly Miller Smith Towers. The Heard Library's ACORN system and the OCLC computer cataloging record will provide international access to the Papers.
We believe that the Kelly Miller Smith Papers constitute the cornerstone of a developing research base documenting the leadership of black individuals and organizations in academic, civic, and church affairs. We thank the Smith Family for their foresight and confidence in placing the Papers at Vanderbilt University in the city that witnessed the efficacy and maturity of the work of Kelly Miller Smith.
Marice Wolfe
Head of Special Collections University Archivist 1988
Introduction To the Kelly Miller Smith Collection
The Kelly Miller Smith Collection of the Jean and Alexander Heard Library at Vanderbilt University fittingly complements the Divinity School's Kelly Miller Smith Institute on the Black Church. The Collection clearly honors the memory of a great religious leader but, just as importantly, it signals the academic value of black religion as a subject matter for teaching and research. We are grateful to Dorothy Ruth Parks, Associate Director and Collections Librarian of the Divinity Library, and Marice Wolfe, University Archivist and Head of Special Collections, for initiating this project; and above all, we are grateful to Mrs. Alice C. Smith for making the collection possible.
Both contemporary and future scholars will view the collection as a valuable resource for inquiring into the thought and practice of a widely esteemed black leader. Happily, Kelly Miller Smith saw the importance of keeping good records and, consequently, the academic community now has access to important primary materials relative to one of the most significant periods in black American history, ca. 1945-1984.
Born and reared in the all-black town of Mound Bayou, Mississippi, the soul of Kelly Miller Smith was shaped by two major institutional responses to the omnipresent reality of racism: namely, the black church and the Knights and Daughters of Tabor. These separate but related institutions instilled in Smith a dialectical tension between inter-racial unity on the one hand and racial separation on the other hand. First, his training in the black church as well as at Morehouse College and Howard University readied him for the leadership of Martin Luther King, Jr., and the philosophy and strategy of the Civil Rights Movement. As a charter member of the Southern Christian Leadership Council and the founder and President of the Nashville Christian Leadership Council, Smith was part of the inner circle of advisors to Martin Luther King, Jr. Second, the Knights and Daughters of Tabor, in which his father held prominent leadership, throughout his life prepared Smith for the black consciousness movement of the late sixties and the concomitant rise of black theology and its institutionalization in the National Conference of Black Churchmen and the Society for the Study of Black Religion. Smith rendered important leadership in both of these organizations. The Smith Collection contains many boxes of materials pertinent to all of the above organizations. The one thing all of these associations shared was their mutual abhorrence of racial discrimination and segregation as paramount evils.
Since Kelly Miller Smith will always be remembered as a great preacher, scholars will not be surprised to find in this Collection a vast reservoir of sermons helpfully cataloged under both title and biblical text. Herein is to be found the substance of Smith's theological and ethical thought as well as the art of his rhetoric, both of which merit critical study. One will also discover his 1983 Lyman Beecher lectures (subsequently published by Mercer University Press under the title Social Crisis Preaching) in various stages of development: lectures in which he attempted to describe the normative foundations for all authentic preaching. Similarly, the Collection also contains numerous speeches, lectures and essays prepared for delivery to many diverse audiences.
Kelly Miller Smith's leadership in the Nashville sit-in movement gained national prominence through an NBC Special White Paper. Both the white and black communities in Nashville will always be indebted to Smith for his prudential leadership in guiding a racially polarized situation to discern and implement justice. His sermon title on the church bulletin board, "Father, Forgive them...." graphically depicted the mood of the Nashville Movement as hundreds of students marched daily from First Baptist Church to sit at lunch counters as a means of protesting racial segregation in public establishments.
Along with numerous relevant materials, this Collection contains several unfinished manuscripts by Smith including one called "The Nashville Story." It is no overstatement to say that between 1960 and 1983 Smith had a hand in every public protest of racism in the city of Nashville as well as on every public policy concerned with racial justice.
Like all black religious leaders, Kelly Miller Smith's ministry was characterized by many diverse functions, offices and associations. But, unlike many, Smith's leadership, more often than not, produced the required results. He was able to mobilize people around issues and inspire them to become actively involved. Many did so simply because he asked them. He seemed always to be calling meetings of one kind or another for purposes of institutional nurture and evaluation, often to start new organizations as a response to some pressing need, and, at other times, to try to revive groups that had fallen into a slump. Numerous files will be found in this Collection on scores of different local, regional, national and international organizations in which Smith enthusiastically rendered some type of leadership. In fact, the Collection offers a road-map of Smith's organizational involvements ranging from denominational activity in the American Baptist Convention, the National Progressive Baptist Convention, the Faith and Order Commission of the World Council of Churches, the National Conference of Black Churchmen, and the National Council of Churches, to service in major civil rights organizations such as the Southern Christian Leadership Council, the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, the National Urban League, the Opportunities Industrialization Center, People United to Save Humanity, several anti-apartheid organizations, various black colleges, and numerous civic, educational and social service organizations. It is important to note that Kelly Miller Smith's ministry clearly demonstrates the integral relation between the church and the community at large. Since the former is the institutional center of the latter nothing can be outside its concern and care. Hence, black ministers must integrate within themselves a broad diversity of functions, offices and interests.
Kelly Miller Smith served as pastor of First Baptist Church, Capitol Hill for thirty-four years. Although the church had a long history of distinguished ministers, Smith's prophetic leadership moved the congregation more significantly than ever before into the arena of public ministry, but not at the expense of basic pastoral care. Rather, his ministry integrated prophetic criticism and pastoral care in all his activities, thus reflecting authentic ministry in the black Christian tradition. This Collection contains comprehensive data relative to the organizational structure and activities of the church, church reports, calendars, organizational objectives and guidelines, music, liturgies, duties and responsibilities of officers, to mention only a few.
Smith's teaching at the American Baptist College of the American Baptist Theological Seminary and at Vanderbilt Divinity School afforded him the opportunity to make an imprint on the ministry of many. It is important to note that in so far as I know he was the first person in the nation to offer a full course on the thought of Howard Thurman. His popularity as a teacher was due in part to the practical wisdom he embodied, his sound judgment about problems of ministry, and his ability to affirm the interests and gifts of every student.
Through the panoramic view that Kelly Miller Smith's papers give us of his thought and ministry, we discover the basic elements of the black church tradition embodied in the preaching, educational and social ministries of this model par excellence.
Peter J. Paris
Elmer G. Homrighausen Professor of Social Ethics Princeton Theological Seminary
- Series I: CORRESPONDENCE
  - Outgoing, October 18, 1945 - Dec 30, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Outgoing, January 3, 1971 - October 18, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Outgoing, December 4, 1978 - August 24, 1983, undated (Box 3)
  - Incoming, Abdullah - Booth, L. (Box 3)
  - Incoming, Booth, W. - Davis, E. (Box 4)
  - Incoming, Davis, F. - Gessell (Box 5)
  - Incoming, Gezork - Hill, A. (Box 6)
  - Incoming, Hill, D. - Jones, C. (Box 7)
  - Incoming, Jones, E. - Malloy (Box 8)
  - Incoming, Malone - Nelson, J. (Box 9)
  - Incoming, Nelson, M. - Rodgerson (Box 10)
  - Incoming, Rogan - Taylor (Box 11)
  - Incoming, Teel - Wiggins (Box 12)
  - Incoming, Wilborn - Zuza (Box 13)
  - Invitations (Box 13)
  - June 7, 1946 - November 23, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - May 22, 1971 - October 15, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Jan 19, 1975 - November 21, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - February 18, 1977 - December 15, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - February 5, 1978 - October 18, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - January 11, 1980 - December 15, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - January 9, 1982 - December 10, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Notebooks kept while a student at Morehouse and Howard Universities (Box 14)
  - Music notebooks and sheet music written by KMS (Box 15)
  - Notebook kept while A Merrill Fellow at Harvard University Diplomas (Box 15)
- BIOGRAPHICAL/PERSONAL
  - Anniversary, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Christmas cards, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1951 - 1958 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1961 - 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1964 - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1971 - 1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1974 - 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1977 - 1978 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1980 - 1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1984 - 1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Magazine articles (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Membership cards (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Biographical profile Tour brochure (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Personal Items (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Autograph book (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Business cards (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Morehouse Commencement (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Personal Items (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Morehouse Graduation Announcement, 1942 Anniversary napkins Patient guest book Business cards (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Personal letterhead (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Poems memorializing KMS (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Introductions written about KMS (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Bulletins/Programs Featuring or Honoring KMS
  - May 14, 1944 - April 26, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - May 17, 1953 - December 4, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - March 28, 1954 - November 27, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - January 3, 1955 - November 27, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - January 4, 1956 - December 31, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - January 20, 1957 - October 27, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - November 11, 1957 - December 23, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - February 9, 1958 - July 13, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - January 11, 1959 - November 29, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - March 27, 1960 - November 20, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - February 19, 1961 - May 19, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - May 21, 1961 - October 8, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - February 11, 1962 - June 3, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - June 10, 1962 - December 25, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - February 17, 1963 - October 28, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - February 9, 1964 - November 22, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - January 17, 1975 - December 12, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - January 1, 1966 - October 23, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - February 21, 1967 - December 17, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - March 10, 1968 - December 15, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - February 9, 1969 - March 30, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - April 13, 1969 - December 3, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - February 1, 1970 - August 23, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - February 14, 1971 - December 12, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - January 1, 1972 - March 26, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - June 18, 1972 - December 17, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - January 14, 1973 - May 12, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - May 13, 1973 - December 31, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - January 8, 1974 - July 5, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - August 11, 1974 - December 29, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - January 11, 1975 - June 29, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - July 19, 1975 - September 7, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - October 10, 1975 - December 6, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - January 11, 1976 - July 12, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - July 3, 1976 - December 14, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - January 16, 1977 - April 23, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - May 1, 1977 - August 20, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - September 24, 1977 - December 18, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - January 7, 1978 - February 27, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - March 26, 1978 - June 25, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - July 7, 1978 - December 20, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - January 1, 1979 - April 30, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - May 6, 1979 - July 29, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - August 5, 1979 - November 16, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - January 13, 1980 - March 12, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - March 17, 1980 - May 18, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - May 25, 1980 - December 17, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - January 19, 1981 - April 27, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - July 22, 1981 - November 7, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - February 8, 1982 - August 2, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - March 4, 1983 - April 29, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - May 6, 1983 - July 24, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - April 1, 1984 - October 20, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Appointment Books, 1965 - 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Books, 1979 - 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Calendar Sheets, 1981 Schedule, 1967 Schedules and Engagements Travel Arrangements (Box 22, Folder 1)
- WRITINGS
  - Sermons, Addresses, Lectures ca., 1948 - 1976
  - 1948 - 1949 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Beauty (I Chronicles 16:29) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Birth of a New Day (John 1:29) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Bluebird of Happiness (Psalm 146:5) Church Economics in Kingdom Building (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1948 - 1949 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Church in Our Today (Luke 4:18) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Consecration through Bible Study (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The EIK! A Symbol of Character (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Forgive Us Our Debts (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1948 - 1949 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - God's Answer: The Negro in History (Matthew 7:20) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Homeless Wanderer (Romans 1:22, 23) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Is it Practical to Read the Bible? (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jesus: A Man of Prayer (Luke 11:1) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Let Brotherly Love Continue (Hebrews 13:1-3) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Let There Be Light (incomplete) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 1948 - 1949 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Microphone Messages (Radio Sermons) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Mind of Jesus (Philippians 2:5) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Relevance of the Ridiculous (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Time Marches On (Proverbs 19:15) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 1950 - 1959 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Daughters of God (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Majesty of Silence (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Why Worship? (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - God in the Morning (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - If Any Man (Matthew 16:24) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Moderator's Address: Eighty-Fourth Annual Session of the Stones River District Association (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Building Together in Human Relations (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Address to the Eighty-Seventh Annual Session of the Stones River District Association (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Moderator's Address: Eighty-Ninth Annual Session of the Stones River District Association (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - August 1, 1960 - June 5, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Speech before the Forty-Seventh Annual Session of the National Dental Association (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Where We Are in Human Relations and Where We Are Going (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Eulogy for Mrs. Maggie Moore Clark (Proverbs 31:3031) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - First Baptist 1965 Lecture Series: Race and the Renewal of the Church - The Pertinence of the Past Stay Tuned for Another World (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - March 29, 1968 - November 24, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Sermon Presented at The Temple, Congregation Ohabai Sholom (Mark 14:12, 14) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - From Futility to Hope (Luke 24: 52, 53) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Facing of This Hour (Genesis 37: 19, 20) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Here Comes the Judge (Romans 2:1-3) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - To Serve the Present Age (II Corinthians 6:2) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Our Unfinished Need (Psalms 51:10) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Love and Fire (I John 4:8; Hebrews 12:29) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Crossroads (Deuteronomy 30:19) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Relevant Extremist (Matthew 5:20) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Songs in the Night (Acts 16:25) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Countdown (Romans 13:11) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Response of Gratitude (Psalms 116:12) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - February 9, 1969 - December 14, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - To Be a Man (I Corinthians 16:13) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Meanwhile (Romans 13:11, 12) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - What Is This Madness? (Acts 26:24) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The Christian Church: Social Thermometer or Thermostat? (Address to the 65th Annual Session of Tennessee Baptist Leadership Education Congress) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Task of Locating God (Job 23:3, 8, 9) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - God of the Whirlwind (Job 38:1) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Response to the Divine Encounter (Job 42:5) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Inquiry Into the Night (Isaiah 21:11, 12) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The Trouble I've Seen (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - March 27, 1970 - December 27, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Death Meets Life (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Black Churches - Black Power (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Liberation (Luke 4:18) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - From Here to Where (Hebrews 11:8) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Ministry in the 70s (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - January 17, 1971 - July 25, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - And Yet, It Is Not Finished (Ezra 5:16) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - How Big Is Your God? (Psalms 139:7) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - No Time for Silence (Luke 14:37-40) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - This God Hates (Proverbs 6:16-19) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - John Doe Alias God (Deuteronomy 8:11-17) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - How to Tell a Christian (John 13:35) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Untitled Sermon (Romans 7:12-25) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - August 1, 1971 - December 5, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - In Remembrance of Me (Luke 22:19) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - A Faith for Those Who Are Trapped (Exodus 14:9-25) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Deeper Response (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Healing Touch (Luke 5:12-16; 8:42-48) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Liberating Gospel (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Towards a Stubborn Hope (Romans 5:3, 4, 5a) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The Bold Ones (Acts 4:13) Untitled Sermon (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - February 7, 1972 - April 30, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Men of God - Right On (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Left-Handed Men (Judges 20:16, 19-20) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Joyful Procession (Psalms 122:1, 2) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Handling Critical Options (Deuteronomy 30:15-30) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Challenge of the Easter Story (Acts 5:29-30) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Valley of Vision (Ezekiel 37:1-14) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - May 7, 1972 - December 31, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - All in the Family (Mark 3:31-35) (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Every Day Will Be Sunday (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Songs in the Night (Job 35:9, 10) (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Miracles and Wonders (Acts 5:12) (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - A Look at Ourselves (II Corinthians 13:5) (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Long Live the King (Matthew 2:1-3) (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Light and Shadows (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - March 4, 1973 - October 14, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Untitled Speech, NAACP Mass Meeting The Words of My Mouth (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - How to Leave Babylon (Isaiah 48:20, 21) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - To Live in His World (Psalms 24:1, 2) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - The Cloud and the Fire (Numbers 9:16) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - If This Be of God (Acts 5:38, 39) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - The Joy and Cast of Commitment (Acts 5:40-42) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - To Cure the Brokenness (John 5:6) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - January 6, 1974 - April 7, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - At This Point in Time (Ecclesiastes 7:10; Psalms 118:24) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - The Urgency of Depth (Luke 5:4) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Songs for the Night Season (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - When God Walks (Genesis 3:1-8) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - To Celebrate, to Cry, and to Act (Luke 19:28-46) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Thanks Be To God (1 Corinthians 2:14-17) (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Untitled Notes (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - May 5, 1974 - November 10, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Agenda for the Condemned (II Timothy 4:6-18) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Forecast - Partly Clear (Genesis 9:13) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Towards Full Surrender (Deuteronomy 6:4 - Leviticus 19:18) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Life Before Death (John 10:10) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Power to Become (John 1:1-13) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Inside-Out Religion (Philippians 4:7) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - To Be Young, Gifted, and Black (I Timothy 4:6-16) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - January 26, 1975 - June 1, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - The Waiting Game (Psalms 62:5-8) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - We Are a Reverent People (Psalms 124:8) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - The Internal Mob (Mark 5:9) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Bright Hope for Tomorrow (I Peter 3:15) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Severe Weather Warning (Acts 27:9-10) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - June 22, 1975 - November 30, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Voice in the Whirlwind (Job 38) (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Soul Force and Social Action, Lay Associates' Conference (Box 23, Folder 18)